The	O
NHS	B-company
has	O
been	O
reformed	O
time	O
and	O
time	O
again	O
.	O

These	O
reforms	O
are	O
simply	O
extensions	O
of	O
the	O
reforms	O
undertaken	O
by	O
New	B-other
Labour	I-other
during	O
the	O
Blair	B-person
years	O
-	O
reforms	O
that	O
by	O
and	O
large	O
,	O
reduced	O
waiting	O
times	O
and	O
improved	O
satisfaction	O
.	O

They	O
're	O
not	O
perfect	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
argue	O
it	O
's	O
too	O
much	O
too	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
people	O
are	O
incapable	O
of	O
disassociating	O
their	O
politics	O
from	O
fact	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
Tories	B-other
and	O
the	O
NHS	B-company
.	O

There	O
is	O
no	O
ideal	O
wonderful	O
NHS	B-company
that	O
we	O
've	O
all	O
been	O
cherishing	O
since	O
WW2	B-other
.	O

Hell	O
,	O
the	O
country	O
has	O
been	O
bitching	O
about	O
the	O
NHS	B-other
for	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
alive	O
.	O
Powerful	O
lobbying	O
forces	O
have	O
linked	O
that	O
with	O
tobacco	O
,	O
when	O
really	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
blamed	O
on	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
our	O
modern	O
lifestyle	O
.	O

Tobacco	O
is	O
a	O
natural	O
plant	O
,	O
smoked	O
by	O
the	O
American	B-other
Indians	I-other
for	O
thousands	O
and	O
thousands	O
of	O
years	O
.	O

I	O
am	O
a	O
whore	O
for	O
Assassin	B-product
's	I-product
Creed	I-product
.	O

I	O
'll	O
pre-order	O
IV	B-product
but	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
pirates	O
makes	O
me	O
wonder	O
how	O
.	O

After	O
the	O
wasted	O
potential	O
of	O
3	B-product
I	O
am	O
not	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
setting	O
.	O

I	O
know	O
I	O
'm	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
bitch	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
hoping	O
for	O
the	O
French	B-other
Revolution	I-other
.	O

With	O
all	O
the	O
historical	O
figures	O
,	O
events	O
(	O
king	O
's	O
flight	O
for	O
e.g	O
)	O
corruption	O
,	O
buildings	O
,	O
.	O

Not	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
the	O
French	B-other
revolution	I-other
is	O
perhaps	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
historical	O
event	O
in	O
history	O
.	O

A	O
rise	O
towards	O
equality	O
and	O
the	O
fall	O
of	O
the	O
Monarchy	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
a	O
government	O
that	O
values	O
individual	O
freedom	O
has	O
Assassin	B-product
's	I-product
Creed	I-product
lore	O
all	O
over	O
it	O
.	O

If	O
the	O
pirate	O
setting	O
fails	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
upset	O
.	O

Fallout	B-product
3	I-product
.	O

Fallout	B-product
:	I-product
New	I-product
Vegas	I-product
.	O

Elder	B-product
Scrolls	I-product
series	I-product
.	O

Warcraft	B-product
series	I-product
(	O
Not	O
World	B-product
of	I-product
)	O
.	O

I	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
time	O
to	O
point	O
out	O
his	O
recent	O
assault	O
on	O
his	O
neighbor	O
after	O
the	O
neighbor	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
driving	O
his	O
new	O
Ferrari	B-product
around	O
their	O
neighborhood	O
like	O
a	O
maniac	O
.	O

China	B-geo-loc
thinks	O
X	O

Muslims	B-other
think	O
Y	O

Israel	B-geo-loc
think	O
Z	O

``	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
look	O
like	O
this	O
model	O
here	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
n't	O
a	O
size	O
4	O
or	O
below	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
n't	O
X	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
n't	O
Y	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
fat	O
worthless	O
piece	O
of	O
shit	O
.	O
''	O

Americans	B-other
are	O
sick	O
of	O
funding	O
Isreal	O
,	O
Iraq	B-geo-loc
,	O
Afghanistan	B-geo-loc
,	O
dirty	O
Pakis	B-other
,	O
Egypt	B-geo-loc
,	O
Europe	B-geo-loc
,	O
Korea	B-geo-loc
,	O
other	O
Americans	B-other
,	O
and	O
everything	O
else	O
.	O

Obama	B-person
let	O
my	O
people	O
go	O
,	O
jk	O
.	O

Kim	B-person
Jong	I-person
un	I-person
appears	O
to	O
his	O
people	O
more	O
than	O
Enda	B-other
ffs	O
.	O

If	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
areas	O
like	O
that	O
where	O
T-Mobile	B-company
reigns	O
supreme	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
awesome	O
.	O

Maybe	O
not	O
the	O
worst	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
thing	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
mind	O
was	O
Johnny	B-person
Depp	I-person
in	O
Transcendence	B-movie
.	O

Do	O
n't	O
forget	O
Nardwuar	B-person
the	I-person
Human	I-person
Serviette	I-person
.	O

I	O
trust	O
the	O
guys	O
at	O
Rockstar	B-company
well	O
enough	O
.	O

Hader	B-person
and	O
Wigg	B-person
were	O
surprisingly	O
good	O
.	O

GoodReads	B-product
is	O
a	O
good	O
suggestion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
recommendations	O
that	O
LibraryThing	B-product
generates	O
to	O
be	O
superior	O

``	O
CNN	B-company
Reporter	O
Blames	O
the	O
Jews	B-other
for	O
Charlie	B-person
Hebdo	I-person
Massacre	O
''	O

Why	O
is	O
it	O
important	O
to	O
the	O
insects	O
at	O
[	O
pjmedia	B-company
?	O
]	O

``	O
Took	O
five	O
Death	B-other
Eaters	I-other
to	O
kill	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
Fabian	B-person
,	O
they	O
fought	O
like	O
heroes	O
...	O
''	O

Coyotes	O
are	O
vermin	O
.	O

But	O
since	O
the	O
HTC	B-product
features	O
a	O
lovely	O
Touchwiz-esque	B-product
android	O
skin	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
gon	O
na	O
need	O
to	O
flash	O
a	O
rom	O
onto	O
it	O
.	O

I	O
made	O
a	O
redheaded	O
dwarf	O
priest	O
in	O
WoW	B-product
and	O
I	O
named	O
her	O
Mollywobbles	B-person
lol	O
.	O

Saying	O
charlie	B-person
is	O
racist	O
is	O
like	O
saying	O
redditors	O
are	O
cats	O
haters	O
.	O

Charlie	B-person
is	O
basically	O
Daily	B-tvshow
Show	I-tvshow
kind	O
of	O
humor	O
.	O

Unless	O
ISIS	B-other
launches	O
an	O
attack	O
on	O
a	O
NATO	B-other
member	O
(	O
which	O
would	O
activate	O
article	O
5	O
)	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
correct	O
.	O

She	O
could	O
take	O
a	O
cue	O
from	O
[	O
Ukraine	B-geo-loc
's	O
parliament	O
]	O

(	O
between	O
Eric	B-person
Schmidt	I-person
,	O
Larry	B-person
Page	I-person
,	O
Sergey	B-person
Brin	I-person
,	O
and	O
this	O
may	O
also	O
be	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Biz	O
to	O
Ethics	O
gradient	O
)	O

Also	O
Han	B-person
Solo	I-person
's	O
transition	O
into	O
a	O
pussy	O
is	O
complete	O
with	O
ROTJ	B-movie
.	O

Get	O
some	O
Bovril	B-product
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
fine	O
.	O

UKIP	B-other
are	O
polling	O
higher	O
than	O
lib	B-other
dems	I-other
by	O
almost	O
double	O

I	O
suppose	O
every	O
ship	O
salvaged	O
that	O
's	O
laden	O
with	O
gold	O
might	O
point	O
to	O
El	B-geo-loc
Dorado	I-geo-loc
as	O
well	O
?	O

Why	O
is	O
that	O
preferred	O
over	O
a	O
funded	O
,	O
well-studied	O
LRT	O
plan	O
that	O
will	O
help	O
more	O
residents	O
than	O
a	O
subway	O
?	O

(	O
the	O
entire	O
higgins	B-person
run	O
)	O

As	O
someone	O
currently	O
working	O
by	O
Battery	B-geo-loc
Park	I-geo-loc
and	O
has	O
a	O
constant	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
lines	O
to	O
Ellis	B-geo-loc
Island	I-geo-loc
/	O
Statue	B-facility
of	I-facility
Liberty	I-facility
from	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
its	O
a	O
big	O
tourist	O
attaction	O

Think	O
about	O
a	O
Christian	O
housewife	O
Consider	O
Noah	B-other
's	I-other
Ark	I-other

So	O
many	O
great	O
memories	O
from	O
Quake	B-product
Lan	O
events	O
.	O

I	O
'll	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
tell	O
both	O
my	O
grandparents	O
that	O
fought	O
in	O
WW2	B-other
that	O
.	O

FOR	O
FUCK	O
'S	O
SAKE	O
,	O
WHO	O
'S	O
RUNNING	O
THIS	O
FUCKIN	O
'	O
TRAILER	O
PARK	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O
?	O
!	O

That	O
's	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
CMHC	B-other
insurance	O
works	O
.	O

Arenal	B-geo-loc
was	O
so	O
beautiful	O
!	O

Hay	O
there	O
,	O
Did	O
n't	O
find	O
a	O
Phobos	B-other
fit	O
so	O
posting	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
the	O
following	O
is	O
any	O
good	O
?	O

